大家好，欢迎收听今日科技播客。今天是2025-06-01，我为大家带来365条最新科技资讯。
首先，让我们来看看今天的重点新闻。
第1条新闻：Obtenha Emojis via Linha de Comando。据Dev。
to报道，Um comando com autocomplete feito com C。
Eu o dia foi bastante tranquilo e aproveitei pra ficar inventando algumas
coisas.
Dentre algumas delas, eu en.
第2条新闻：Get Emojis via Command Line。据Dev。
to报道，A command with autocomplete made with C。
Today was pretty calm, so I spent some time tinkering with ideas.
Among them, I found a link to a bunch of em.
第3条新闻：Stranger Things season 5 will stream this November。
据The Verge报道，Stranger Things fifth and final season finally has a premiere date。
During its live Tudum event, Netflix announced that Stranger Things fifth season
w.
第4条新闻：A beginner's guide to the Ltx-Video-0。9.
7 model by Lightricks on Replicate.据Dev。
to报道，This is a simplified guide to an AI model called Ltx-Video-0。9.
7 maintained by Lightricks.
If you like these kinds of analysis, you should join AImode.
第5条新闻：Wednesday Season 2s Opening Scenes Introduce Us to Her Wild Summer。
据Gizmodo报道，Tim Burton's Netflix show starring Jenna Ortega drops part one August
6 and part two September 3。
接下来是今日科技快讯。
快讯1：Quantum Financial System vs. Traditional Banking: A Comparative Analysis。
快讯2：Daily Debug  Day 1: Blocks in Motion。
快讯3：Stranger Things Returns for One Last Time This November。
以上就是今天的科技资讯播报。感谢大家的收听，我们明天同一时间再见。